Asher Levin

High Bridge, NJ 08829 asher.levin@yahoo.com

+1 908 638 6954

Asher Levin is a 20-year-old living in High Bridge, NJ. Having completed associate degree in Information Technology from RVCC with a 3.77 GPA. He enrolled at Kean University for a Bachelors Degree in Information Technology. With experience in information technology, food service, customer service, and social work.

Work Experience

Community Resource Specialist

HUNTERDON HELPLINE-Flemington, NJ August 2022 to Present

- Database Entry
- Usage of Microsoft Word, Excel, and Access on a day to day basis
- Phone communication with clients and information collection

Crew Member

Dunkin' Donuts-Clinton, NJ October 2020 to July 2022

- Working as a customer service representative.
- Filling orders of food and drink.
- taking calls from affiliate companies about shipments of product.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Information System and Technology (AS)

Kean University - Union, NJ

February 2024 to Present

Associates Degree in Information Systems and Technology (AS)

Raritan Valley Community College - Branchburg, NJ

August 2021 to July 2023

3.77 GPA

Skills

- Experience with Windows (5 years)
- Desire to Learn
- Serving Experience (2 years)
- Food Production (2 years)
- Experience with Microsoft Word, Excel (5 years)

- Data Entry (1 year)
- Data Collection (1 year)
- Computer Networking